[Music]
MP3
Kara Do Hello Hello
everyone Welcome to my YouTube
channel Our topic today is HE
File Number about your health product
If you haven't seen our last video
which is about Your Help Plus then
you
can definitely subscribe to it in the link description which we have
appointed will help you a lot
Selecting now we are talking
about health benefits
So in the inbuilt feature your first
treatment cover is free hospitalization
your 30s post hospitalization is 6 days
see this is equal to free
existing if you have any disease before taking the policy
and the company subscribes
then you can subscribe so
Ayurveda treatment is covered now
tourism in short but in this you must keep one thing in
mind that it should be done only
in a government hospital or
in a government approved center
treatment subscribe and subscribe is that
whichever is not according to you Let's talk about additional SP
Now limited benefits
appointment means that as soon as this year ends Sameer
with hatred and first this year  It used to happen only
once in the time period, now it is a
very good valid feature available for protection of treatment. In this,
you must keep one thing in mind that
reset benefits do
not provide coverage to de Villiers on behalf of the same person.
Treatment treatment means that
if there is any such situation in front of them, hospitalization is
available that youth can subscribe to it. Let's
talk about the next feature which is
your exam balance cover up.
Air ambulance coverage is available in this product
and the biggest plus point is that if you
subscribe to this channel of Agni Yudh,
it means you appoint a screen protector, then the
company used to remove you
that if you have an expense of Rs 5000, then
your tempered glass was complete.
Now, if you do
not subscribe, if the subscription is
cancelled, then your ten percent no claim
bonus will be deducted.
If you subscribe, you will get an ambulance on Thursday. If you are subscribed, then
hospitalization celebration is
available to you. Now let's talk about this feature, value
added service.
Online chat is available on the subscribe side, you can pin it up
with the doctor.  Dietitian available in
Delhi Hospital Delhi means that
you
get a Gabbu every day when you are admitted in the hospital, then the
claim for your treatment is made by the company,
plus additional daily allowance is provided to you
if your policy is of Rs 5 lakh then you
can take Rs 1000, if it is of Rs 7 lakh then go ahead
and if you subscribe, you can
apply for Next 9 news coverage after 3 years, if you are for Rs 5 lakh you can do
normal delivery or caesarean delivery of up
to Rs 25000, if you
start subscribing then you can claim a maximum of Rs 1000,
if the policy details are there then Rs 25000
is yours for normal delivery and Rs 1500 is yours for
caesarean delivery, you can click on it
and again it is available for treatment of Rs 10051,
if your policy is of Rs 5 lakh or more then
you can do it by shifting to normal delivery
but  If there was a request for subscription,
you
can do it for up to 1 lakh. Now let's talk about optional. You
can add it to the job skin of a teacher.
First of all, tractor
means whatever you
can like and subscribe to, which the company does
not space. Therefore, if you read it at this time, then
you do not have to make this payment. The
company does that.
Second is your time injury protector.
But time protector means that
if a policy holder's policy is
not getting fulfilled due to some reason or due to some reason, then at
one point their amount starts to seem
very less. But if this
product is available, then you can add
bonus every year in the subscribed policy. Click here.
You can
subscribe. Subscribe.
All these optional features that you can add to this policy are
very good policies designed to
increase and such loot. ICC is a very travel company,
so you can trust it. Claim
settlement is also very good. So this was all the
information about ICICI Lombard's health
and  We keep bringing information about how to use the product,
so please
like and subscribe to our channel,
thank you for watching.